Hello friends, how do you understand, everything must
be fine, friends, we keep talking about the TV industry every day,
I
talk about scooters, we talk about new investments, we
also talk about vehicles with new IC engines, but
we do not talk about some things,
that RTO cruise because safety is the
number one priority, when driving a vehicle, no matter how it is, it is
very important to have a safe shift and
in such a situation, a very good
update has come from the government, it is for those people who have
children at home, that is, children below four years of age
and you drive a two-wheeler, then
this is a new rule, it is a bit strict
but yes, it has been implemented, it is implemented today
and it is finally applicable in every state,
what is the rule, let's talk about that, do
watch this video till the end, do not
press the subscribe button of the channel, let's
start, so friends, the Ministry
of Road Transport and Highways has implemented a new
rule for the two-wheelers, those who
drive a vehicle, have children below four years of age at home, so
here a new safety rule has come
that now you will have to save your child from a
loss, now
What is a harness, how does it look, I will
tell you later. Along with the harness, you will also have to get a
helmet for children. The small ones from World Cycle,
you will have to make them for
your children. If you have
not worn this harness and helmet, then you will have to pay a
huge penalty, a penalty of
₹1000.
If you
subscribe and are taking it on a ride, then
you should subscribe
that your license will be suspended
and the next rule is that if there is a
child below four years of age in your vehicle, then the
speed of your vehicle should
not be more than 100 km per hour. Even if it is more, the
traffic police can issue you a challan
and this is legal because the rule of this thing has come.
Now the question comes that how does a harness look,
how do you take it? Friends, I will
show you this photo. It is visible on the side, so I will
show it on the screen as well. This is how it happens,
basically a Khan
share back will be typed on the waist, in which the child means the
child is connected to you. If any
accident happens, then the child will be tagged with you. It is not like this if
you have gone somewhere else.
Subscribe This is
very important, yes it is very
important, the government has made it mandatory
and this rule has become applicable if you are
travelling with a child below four years of age on a two wheeler, then purchase this thing
first, otherwise you will be fined Rs. 1000
along with this your license will be suspended for 3 months
and let me tell you
that there is a quality in the harness as well, let
me tell you what is the
quality, first of all it should be soft, there should
not be anything that the child should not feel,
plus it should be so fit that the
child does not move here and there, so keep all these
things in mind, you should purchase this harness,
if you have a four year old child in your house
and you take him in the car, do
this first in your free time, let
me tell you one more thing that when
you go on a bike and you
can make the children sit on the front tank, that too has become illegal,
from today onwards you cannot make the children sit in the front,
you will have to make them sit in the back, if you do this during fever then there is a
definition on that, so this is
some update date  It has come recently today. If
you liked the informative video
then please like it, otherwise
subscribe. You will get the price
in the next video. Jai Hind Jai Ho
[Music]